Garson: Welcome, please come in.
Mesut & Şenol: Thank you.
Garson: What would you like?
Şenol: Can we see the menu first?
Garson: Of course. Here is our menu.
Şenol: Thanks.
Garson: Have you decided, sir?
Mesut: I want lentil soup, chicken, and rice.
Şenol: I want tomato soup and döner.
Şenol: Let's also get a salad to share.
Garson: Certainly, sir. What would you like to drink?
Mesut: I'll have ayran.
Şenol: Make mine orange juice.
Garson: Would you also like dessert after the meal?
Garson: We have very nice desserts.
Mesut: What desserts do you have?
Garson: We have baklava, rice pudding, and kadayıf.
Mesut: Let's have one portion of baklava each after the meal.
Mesut: With tea on the side.
Garson: Alright, sir. I'll bring your orders right away.
Garson: Yes. These are yours. And these are yours.
Garson: Enjoy your meal, sir.
Mesut: Waiter, the bill please!
Garson: Here you go.
Mesut: Keep the change.
Garson: Thanks.